♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 15=
Miss Song,
I advise you not to act rashly.
As an opera singer,
I'm not good with guns.
It could easily go off.
Are you alright?
Take her to the Governor Mansion.
- Yes.
You were too reckless today.
You nearly died.
Were you foolish or brave?
I owe you for this.
I'll definitely repay it.
(Governor Mansion)
(Execute the Father-Killer)
Governor Mansion colludes
with a merchant,
protecting a father-killer
and utterly ignoring the people!
Hand over Jiang Chun'er now!
Execute Jiang Chun'er!
The President Jiang's murder case
is still ongoing.
Besides, this is the Governor Mansion.
How dare you run wild here!
Is there no law in Fengcheng?
To rise to power, Xu You'an
bribed an opera singer
to murder his foster father
on his wedding day.
It's heinous!
He is a demon with blood on his hands.
Now he's shielding Jiang Chun'er
and colluding with her.
He's pushing us common people
to the brink of despair!
Exactly!
Execute Jiang Chun'er!
Come out! Come out!
Daring to cause trouble
in front of Governor Mansion?
Do you all have a death wish?
Fellow townsfolk,
we must get an answer today!
Otherwise, he'll have us all dead
and our houses torn apart by tomorrow!
He's the son of a dancing girl!
Isn't a dancing girl just a prostitute?
Can a prostitute bear a decent child?
I advise you not to let others use you.
The murderer in President Jiang's case
is someone else.
You are the disciple
of the serial killer, Zhao Shengge.
You are both devils
persecuting us common people!
Fellow townsfolk, neither of them
is anything good!
Stone him to death!
Stone them to death!
Not good ones!
Neither of them are good!
Brat of a prostitute!
Stone them to death!
Xu You'an, it seems
they're coming for you.
Don't act rashly.
Don't run!
Not good ones!
Scoundrel!
Beat him to death!
Don't go!
You're heartless!
Come back here!
(Governor Mansion)
Why look into the Xu family
and the Rongqing Troupe?
Because
I'm too infatuated with you.
You're engaged to the Miss Jiang.
If I wanted to be your wife,
I'd have to dig up everything
I could on my love rival.
Cut the crap.
I don't buy that.
If you don't tell the truth,
our torture methods here
are not something
a fragile woman like you can bear.
Governor,
this is what we found
at Song Mianxiang's residence.
Announce to the public now
that Song Mianxiang is the real killer.
And tell everyone the execution
will be at noon tomorrow.
Yes.
Right. The one leading the mob
has already confessed.
The Xiaosheng Society's Du Xiaolin
instigated them.
(Him again.)
(After the matter of Chun'er is settled,)
(the first thing I'll eliminate
is the Xiaosheng Society.)
Replace all the ammunition
for tomorrow's execution with blanks.
Alright.
You intend to let Song Mianxiang off?
She killed Jiang Xiaoren.
That's like avenging my mother.
Besides,
she's not at fault.
So you're such a righteous
and understanding man.
Poor me, misunderstood
by you for so long,
I never even got an apology.
You kept calling me "lackey" before,
so let's call it even.
Drink some water.
No.
I want to go with Mother.
Mother.
Nowadays, many high officials and nobles
like opera singers like you.
Teach them to sing opera.
Otherwise, I'll kill them all.
I won't do that.
You're utterly devoid of conscience.
You used me to curry favor.
I will absolutely not join you
in harming those innocent girls.
What are you doing?
No!
I'll teach them.
So, that girl from eight years ago
was Song Mianxiang.
This way!
Hurry!
Here she is.
You dare to run?
You're dead, you brat!
Move!
Get up!
Let me go!
Move!
I didn't expect you to visit
such a filthy place, Miss Jiang.
I'm sorry.
If I hadn't let them find you back then,
you could've escaped
the Jiang residence.
You recognized me?
Since you recognized me,
how dare you come alone?
Aren't you afraid I'll kill you?
I came to apologize to you.
As expected, a naive young lady.
What do I need your apology for?
If it weren't for you back then,
I would've escaped that den of devils.
After I was caught,
I nearly got beaten to death.
I'm sorry.
I owe it all to you.
I will definitely compensate you.
Compensate?
This case must have a killer.
Can you die in my place?
I can.
You're crazy.
It was me who wronged you.
It was my family who wronged you.
This is the only thing I can do.
Take this.
Put on my clothes.
Leave Fengcheng.
Go to a place where no one knows you.
And live the life you deserve.
You want to die?
I'll grant your wish.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪